Fran is having a story with the
está teniendo una historia Fran con los
Spanish television people now Fran was
de televisión española ahora Fran estaba
very angry because they had used
muy porque habían utilizado las
Pablo's images and he hadn't given his
imágenes de Pablo y él no había dado
consent no and when I went in there
consentimiento no y cuando entro yo ahí
and I found out what had happened look at
y me entero de lo que había pasado mira
Pablo's face at the end they put
la cara de Pablo a ti al final te meten
all the And what is the reason for
todos los Y a qué se debe la carita de
my Pablo's little face Of course when I'm
mi Pablo A que claro cuando yo me estoy
seeing myself there that they are there well we are going to
viendo ahí que están ahí pues vamos a
sue Spanish television because they have
demandar televisión española porque han
taken my images I say Pablo Let's see
cogido mis imágenes digo Pablo A ver es
something happens man Well this one had
que pasa una cosa tío Bueno este me
written to me the one in the morning
había me había escrito la de mañanero
I need to broadcast these images I don't know what I don't
necesito emitir estas imágenes no sé qué
know how much something like that No well I say to him
no sé cuánto algo así No pues yo le digo
hello Alexandra can you put it on without any
hola Alexandra podéis ponerla sin
problem
problema
Thanks [ __ ] what has Pablo seen Pablo
Gracias que ha visto Pablo Pablo
has seen something that they asked
ha visto algo que le pidieron permiso a
Javi's permission to use the video And Javi
Javi para utilizar el vídeo Y Javi lo
gave it I wish you had sued he says I
dio Ojalá hubierais demandado dice me
would have laughed my ass off what an [ __ ] you did
hubiera descojonado qué cabrón sí que
give permission [ __ ] how the people who
diste permiso Cabrón cómo la gente que
say that they have to sue me those are
dice que me tienen que demandar esa es
good people Javi Go [ __ ] yourself I'm
buena gente Javi Vete a tomar por el
sure he says he's good people
culo seguro que dice que es buena gente
because they have invited him sometime
porque le han invitado alguna vez a él
this wasn't the dog from Dallas this  This
este no era el perro de Dallas este este
was not a
no era un